You are part of the back-end development team of the next Facebook. You are given a line of usernames,
between one of the following symbols:
 space, “/”, “\”, “(“, “)”. First you have to export all valid usernames.
A valid username starts with a letter and can contain only letters,
 digits and “_”. It cannot be less than 3 or
more than 25 symbols long. Your task is to sum the length of every 2 consecutive valid usernames
 and print
on the console the 2 valid usernames with biggest sum of their lengths, each on a separate line.
Expected 
input: ds3bhj y1ter/wfsdg 1nh_jgf ds2c_vbg\4htref
Expected output:
wfsdg
ds2c_vbg
§
ds3bhj y1ter/wfsdg 1nh_jgf ds2c_vbg\4htref
§
wfsdg
ds2c_vbg