You are given a text and a number.% The text can contain any characters:% (digits, Latin letters (both capital and letter
 case) or any other symbols). The character '@' is special – it marks the end of the text.% 
Your task is to iterate the text and to perform an operation for every character.% Having a RESULT = 0, the operations
 are as follows:%
•	If the current character is '@', stop the program and print the value of RESULT
•	If the current character is a digit (‘0’ – ‘9’), then multiply the RESULT by this digit
•	If the current character is a letter, add its index from the Latin alphabet to RESULT.% 
o	'A' has an index 0, ‘B’ has an index 1, etc…%
•	If the current character is a symbol, that is different from the ones described above, create module of the 
RESULT
 by the provided number (M)
•	See the sample input/output for more detailed explanation
§
2001
%
Hello .NET 5! My name is Peter 8-)@
§
518

