You are given a number (SECRET) and a text.% The text must be encoded using the SECRET.%
The encoding is done as follows:%
•	If the character is “@”, stop the program
•	If the character in the text is a letter, multiply its char code by the given SECRET and add 1000.%
•	If the character in the text is a digit, add to its char code SECRET and add 500
•	If the character in the text is not a digit, letter or “@” (any other symbol), subtract from its char code SECRET

•	After performing the above operations on the character in the original text:
o	If the character is on even position in the text - divide the encoded value by 100 and round the precision to 2
 digits after the decimal point
o	Else if the character is on odd position in the original text – multiply its encoded value by 100
o	The first character in the text is at position 0.% 
Your task is to encode a text, using the rules above.%
§
10
C#1 is pretty easy exam@ 
§
16.70
2500
5.59
2200
20.50
215000
0.22
212000
21.40
201000
21.60
216000
22.10
2200
20.10
197000
21.50
221000
0.22
201000
22.00
197000
20.90



