Write a program that reads a rectangular integer matrix of size N x M and finds in it the square 3 x 3 that has maximal sum of its elements. 
On the first line, you will receive the rows N and columns M. On the next N lines you will receive each row with its columns.
Print the elements of the 3 x 3 square as a matrix, along with their sum.
Expected input:
4 5
1 5 5 2 4
2 1 4 14 3
3 7 11 2 8
4 8 12 16 4
Expected output:
Sum = 75
1 4 14
7 11 2
8 12 16
§
4 5%
1 5 5 2 4%
2 1 4 14 3%
3 7 11 2 8%
4 8 12 16 4%
§
Sum = 75%
1 4 14%
7 11 2%
8 12 16