Consider the following simple algorithm for encoding (i.e. compressing) text:%
•	Count the occurrences of each symbol in each symbol in the text
o	i.e. the “frequency” of a symbol in the text
•	The most frequent symbol will be encoded with a single bit “1”
•	The second most frequent will be encoded with two bits: “11”
•	i.e. if we order the symbols by their frequency, having the most frequent symbol at position 1 and the least
 frequent symbol at position N:%
o	the 1st symbol has a code of one bit with a value of 1
o	the 2nd symbol has a code of two bits with a value of 1
o	…
o	the ith symbol has a code of i bits with a value of 1
o	…
o	the Nth symbol has a code of N bits with a value of 1
•	Go through the text and encode each symbol according to its code from the above rules
o	Separate encoded symbols by placing a single “0” bit between them
o	E.g. if the symbol “a” has to be encoded with the code “1” and “b” has to be encoded with the code “11”, then the 
text “ab” will be encoded as “1011”
•	The encoded text is then padded with zeroes to the right, so its total length is divisible by 8 (the size of a 
byte)
o	E.g. for the previous example, where the entire encoded text was “1011”, it will be padded right with 4 zeroes,
 giving “10110000”
•	The entire encoded text is split into groups of 8 symbols and each of the groups is turned into a 1-byte unsigned 
integer value (i.e. “parsed” from binary into a byte-sized integer)
o	For the previous example, where the encoded and padded text was “10110000”, there will be exactly 1 group, so 
the end result will be a single byte integer: 176
?	The leftmost bit is considered the most-significant
•	After all the values for the encoded text, we append the code table
o	The code table is a series of lines, each of which a concatenation of a symbol and a number, representing the
length of its code
o	E.g. from the previous example the text “ab” will have the following code table:%
?	a1
b2
?	Note: the code length could be more than 1 digit, e.g. a text with the English alphabet, the last line of the
 code table will be “z26”
•	A broader example: say we have the text “abaaba”. %
o	The most frequent symbol is “a”, followed by “b”.%
o	“a” will have the code “1” and “b” will have the code “11”
o	The encoded text will be “1011010101101”, which has a length of 13
o	The encoded text will be padded right with 3 zeroes, giving “1011010101101000”
o	“1011010101101000” will be divided into two groups of 8 symbols:%
?	 “10110101” and
?	 “01101000”
o	“10110101” will be turned into the integer 181 and “01101000” will be turned into the integer 104
o	The end result is the entire text (which was 6 character values) encoded in two bytes, ordered like so:% 181 104
o	Of course, we append the code table (each symbol with its code) after the text itself

Now, that’s all well and good, but what’s the use of encoded text if you can’t decode it? That’s where you come in.
Your task is to write a program, which given an encoded by the above rules text (as series of integers, followed by a 
series of lines of a code table) decodes the integers and prints the original text.
Input
The input data should be read from the console.%
On the first line of the input, there will be a sequence of integers, separated by spaces (representing the encoded text)
On the next line, there will be a single integer number L – the number of lines in the code table	
On each of the next L lines there will be a string.% 
•	The first symbol of the string describes which symbol from the text this line of the table represents.% 
•	All of the remaining symbols will be digits, representing a number (most significant digit is the second symbol in the string), equal to the length of the code for the symbol in the text
The input data will always be valid and in the format described. There is no need to check it explicitly.%
Output
The output data should be printed on the console. Print exactly one line – the original text (decoded)
Constraints
•	The original text will be no more than 4000 symbols
•	Each symbol in the original text will have an ASCII code from 0 to 255
?
173 222 
4
 2
a1
b3
c4
?
aa bc