Doge is a very popular dog.% He is so popular that there is a crypto currency named after him.% The crypto currency is
 named DogeCoin. Doge loves his DogeCoins and wants to gather as much as he can.% Help this cute little animal.%
Doge and the DogeCoins are placed on a grid consisting of NxM cells (N vertical cells, numbered from 0 to N-1 and M
 horizontal cells, numbered from 0 to M-1).% Doge is always placed on location [0; 0].% Doge is allowed only to move in 
two directions (right and down).%
There are K coins on the grid.% Two or more coins may be on the same location. There also might be a coin(s) where Doge 
starts (0, 0) and he automatically gathers them.%
Find the biggest possible amount of coins that Doge can gather when moving only down and right.%
Output
The output should be printed on the console.%
Output the biggest possible amount of coins that Doge can gather when moving only down and right.%
§
10 10%
11%
0 0%
1 1%
2 2%
3 3%
4 4%
5 5%
6 6%
7 7%
8 8%
8 9%
9 9%
§
11