You are given a matrix of numbers.% By given the pattern below, find the pattern with maximal sum:%
The pattern consists of neighbor cells in the matrix.% The numbers in the cells must be consecutive, i.e.% the following 
rules must be always valid:%
A = B -1, B = C – 1, C = D – 1, D = F – 1, F = E – 1, E = G - 1
The size of the pattern is constant and always has the given form.%
Example:%
The patterns here are marks with green, blue and yellow colors:%
•	The green pattern has a sum of its numbers 35
•	The blue pattern has a sum of its numbers 56
•	The yellow pattern has a sum of its numbers -14
The winning pattern is the blue with maximal sum of 56
§
5
1 2 3 4 5
2 3 4 5 6
3 4 5 6 7
4 5 6 7 8
5 6 7 8 9  
§
YES 42