Given several paragraphs (lines) of text and a search word, the relevance index of a paragraph is the number of
occurrences of that search word (as a separate word) in the paragraph. Here, comparison is case insensitive, i.e. the
 only thing that is important is the words have the same letters, ignoring casing.%
Hence, ordering text by relevance index means creating a new text and
•	Finding the paragraph in the with the highest relevance index (in the old text) and placing it first
•	Then finding the paragraph with the second-highest relevance index (in the old text) and placing it second 
•	and so on
You are tasked with ordering paragraphs by relevance index, given a search word. Furthermore, all letters of all
 occurrences of the search word must be made uppercase in the resulting ordered text and any punctuation should be
removed and words should be separated by a single space.%
The paragraphs can contain English letters (upper- and lower-case), spaces and punctuation to separate words.%
 Punctuation characters are: ",", ".", "(", ")", ";", "-", "!", "?" (comma, dot, parentheses, semicolon, dash, exclamation mark, question mark).
Input
The input data should be read from the console.%
On the first line of the input, there will be a single string – the search word.%
On the second line there will be a single integer number L – the number of paragraphs in the text.%
On each of the next L lines there will be a single string – the text in the respective paragraph.%
The input data will always be valid and in the format described. There is no need to check it explicitly.%
Output
The output data should be printed on the console. Print exactly L lines – the paragraphs with removed punctuation,
 each two words separated by a single space and the words matching the search word converted to uppercase.%
Constraints
•	L will be no more than 100
•	Each line will be no longer than 1000 characters
•	Each symbol in the original text will have an ASCII code from 0 to 255
•	Time limit: 0.10 seconds
•	Memory limit: 16 MB
?
text
5
if you have someone to text
but the text is more than text to text
and you need a better text to text
try to text what the text would want to text another text with text
cause this text is too much about text, and a text will never teach you how to text
?
try to TEXT what the TEXT would want to TEXT another TEXT with TEXT
cause this TEXT is too much about TEXT and a TEXT will never teach you how to TEXT
but the TEXT is more than TEXT to TEXT
and you need a better TEXT to TEXT
if you have someone to TEXT
