Solving one task is too mainstream. You are given two tasks. Solve them both.%
First task
A strange street is filled with lamps numbered 1 through N, initially all turned off.% Joro has birthday and wants to 
turn on all the lamps. He makes multiple actions turning the lights on, beginning with lamp 1. On the first action, he 
turns on the first lamp, and every 2nd lamp that is turned off thereafter. On the 2nd action, he turns on the first lamp
 that is turned off, and every third lamp that is turned off thereafter.% In general, on the ith action, he turns on the 
first lamp that is turned off, and every (i+1)th lamp that is still turned off thereafter.
For example, with 8 lamps, on the first action Joro turns on 1, 3, 5 and 7, leaving 2, 4, 6, and 8. On the second action
 he turns on 2 and 8, leaving 4 and 6. On the third action he turns on lamp 4, and on the final action lamp 6.
You will be given N, the number of lamps. Find the number of the lamp turned on last.%	
Second task
Robot Joro (“Joro the bot”) is standing on some arbitrary point in the infinite plane.%
Joro is given a sequence of commands that he has to execute. The commands are given as a string. Each character of this 
string is a single command.% The commands must be executed in the given order.%
There are 3 types of commands: 'S' means "step forward", 'L' means "turn 90 degrees to the left", and 'R' means "turn 90
 degrees to the right". All steps that Joro makes have the same length.%
Since Joro is a bot, he will be executing the commands forever: after he executes the last character of the commands,
 he will always start from the beginning again.
We say that Joro’s path is bounded if there is some positive real number R such that while executing the infinite 
sequence of steps he will never leave the circle with radius R steps and center at his starting location.
Given the list of commands (as a single line string), your program should determine whether Joro’s path will be bounded
 or not. Print the string "bounded" (quotes for clarity) if the path is bounded and "unbounded" if it is not.
Input
The input data should be read from the console.%
Your program should solve one input of the first task and two inputs of the second task.%
The number of lamps N will be given on the first input line.%
A string of commands for Robot Joro will be given on the second input line.%
Another string of commands for Robot Joro will be given on the third input line.%
Joro executes the two strings of commands separately!
The input data will always be valid and in the format described. There is no need to check it explicitly.%
Output
The output data should be printed on the console.%
On the first output line print the solution of the first task.%
On the second output line your program should print the solution of the second task with the input data from the second
 input line.%
On the third output line your program should print the solution of the second task with the input data from the third 
input line.%
Constraints
•	N will be between 1 and 2 000 000, inclusive.%
•	The number of commands for Robot Joro will be between 1 and 2500, inclusive (for each test).%
•	Allowed working time for your program: 0.1 seconds. Allowed memory: 16 MB.%
§
12
L
SRSL
§
12
bounded
unbounded

