Write a program that reads a keyword and some text from the console and prints all sentences from the text, containing that word.% A sentence is any sequence of words ending with '.', '!' or '?'.% Examples:
§
Expected input:	
This is my cat! And this is my dog. We happily live in Paris – the most beautiful city in the world! Isn’t it great? Well it is :)	
§
Expected output:
This is my cat!
And this is my dog.
